(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T21:13:02.307917",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
幽閉利口 逝く前に
Before locking up the clever one to die,
ユーヘイじぁ利口に難儀ダーリン
Being locked up makes it tough to play smart, darling.
幽閉ストップ 知ってないし
Stop locking me up, I didn't know!
勘弁にしといてなんて惨忍
"Give me a break," you say, how cruel.
人様願う欠片のアイロニー
The ironies people wish for in fragments,
誰もが願う無機質のような
That lifeless thing that everyone wishes for,
一足先に始めてたいような
Wanting to get a head start on it,
先が見えないヴァージンハッピーショー
An unpredictable virgin happy show.
無いの新たにお願い一つ
I don't have a single brand-new wish,
愛も変わらずおまけに
Love remains unchanged, and as a bonus,
ワーニング ワーニング
Warning, warning.
無いのあなたにお願い一つ
I have just one wish for you,
張り詰めた思い込め
Putting all my built-up feelings into it.
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side,
歯をむき出して パッパッパッ
Baring your teeth, pa-pa-pa.
照れくさいね
It's so embarrassing, isn't it?
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side,
歯を突き出して パッパッパッ
Sticking out your teeth, pa-pa-pa.
ハハ
Haha.
You are KING
無邪気に遊ぶ
Playing innocently,
期待 期待のダーリン ダーリン
Expecting, full of expectation, darling, darling.
健気に笑う 痛い 痛いの消える
Smiling bravely, making the pain, the pain go away.
無惨に死ねる 苦い思いも無くなって
Dying miserably, all bitter feelings vanishing,
ラララブ ラッタッタ
La-la-love, rat-tat-ta.
嫌い 嫌いの最低 泣いてダウン
Hating, hating at its worst, crying and down.
毎度新たにお願い一つ
Every time, a brand-new wish,
愛も変わらずピックアップの
Love remains unchanged in this pickup of a
ワーニング ワーニング
Warning, warning.
無いのあなたにお願い一つ
I have just one wish for you,
張り詰めた思い込め
Putting all my built-up feelings into it.
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side,
歯をむき出して パッパッパッ
Baring your teeth, pa-pa-pa.
邪魔くさいね
How bothersome, isn't it?
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side,
歯を突き出して パッパッパッ
Sticking out your teeth, pa-pa-pa.
ハハ
Haha.
You are KING
幽閉利口 逝く前に
Before locking up the clever one to die,
ユーヘイじぁ利口に難儀ダーリン
Being locked up makes it tough to play smart, darling.
幽閉ストップ 知ってないし
Stop locking me up, I didn't know!
勘弁にしといてなんて惨忍
"Give me a break," you say, how cruel.
人様願う欠片のアイロニー
The ironies people wish for in fragments,
誰もが願う無機質のような
That lifeless thing that everyone wishes for,
一足先に始めてたいような
Wanting to get a head start on it,
先が見えないヴァージンハッピーショー
An unpredictable virgin happy show.
無いの新たにお願い一つ
I don't have a single brand-new wish,
愛も変わらずおまけに
Love remains unchanged, and as a bonus,
ワーニング ワーニング
Warning, warning.
無いのあなたにお願い一つ
I have just one wish for you,
張り詰めた思い込め
Putting all my built-up feelings into it.
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side,
歯をむき出して パッパッパッ
Baring your teeth, pa-pa-pa.
照れくさいね
It's so embarrassing, isn't it?
レフトサイド ライトサイド
Left side, right side,
歯を突き出して パッパッパッ
Sticking out your teeth, pa-pa-pa.
ハハ
Haha.
You are KING
みんなー！
Hey everyone!
生誕祭2026に駆けつけてくれてありがとうー！
Thank you for rushing over to Birthday Fest 2026!
盛り上がる準備、出来てるかー！
Are you ready to get hyped?!
ぶち上げていくぞー！
Let me turn this up!
でも、ちょっと今から急いでライブ会場にみんなを連れて行かなきゃなんないから、一緒に行ってくれるか？
But I gotta hurry and take everyone to the concert venue right now, so will you come with me?
行くぞー！
Let's go!
熱くなった銀のメタリックハート
My heated-up silver metallic heart
導火線に火をつけてあげる
I'll light its fuse for you
不思議なほどハイな気分さ
I'm feeling strangely high
砂埃を巻き上げて行こう
Let's kick up the dust and keep going
悲鳴をまじらせ暴走する鼓動
Screams mixed with a runaway heartbeat
目の前にはミサイルの雨
A rain of missiles right in front of us
アドレナリンずっと流して
Keeping the adrenaline flowing non-stop
僕の方がオーバーヒートしそう
I feel like I'm the one about to overheat
爆発して灰になっても
Even if I explode and turn into ashes
このままだと笑ってるね きっと
I'm sure I'll still be laughing just like this
街を追い越して この世の果てまで
Overtaking the city, all the way to the end of the world
ぶっ飛ばして心中しよう さぁ手を伸ばして!
Speeding away, let's go down together, reach out your hands!
地平線に届くように
To reach the horizon
限界まで振り切ってくれ
Push it to the absolute limit
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
最高のフィナーレを! Yeah!
Give us the grand finale! Yeah!
もう数えるくらいで僕らは消え失せて
In just a few counts, we will disappear
真暗な朝が来るね
And a pitch-black morning will come
お気に入りの服に さぁ着がえたなら駆け出して!
Once you've changed into your favorite clothes, run out!
あきれるほど声を上げて
Shout at the top of your lungs
大気圏を突破しようぜ
Let's break through the atmosphere
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
鋼の翼で
On wings of steel
駆けぬけてよ 時間切れまで
Run through until time runs out
生まれつきのスピード狂なのさ
I'm a born speed demon after all
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
来世でまた会おう Yeah!
See you in the next life, yeah!
広い宇宙の 数あるひとつ
In this vast universe, among the countless ones,
青い地球の 広い世界で
On this wide world of the blue Earth,
小さな恋の 思いは届く
My small love's feelings will reach
小さな島の あなたのもとへ
To you on that small island.
あなたと出会い 時は流れる
Meeting you, time flows by,
思いを込めた 手紙もふえる
And letters filled with my feelings increase.
いつしか二人 互いに響く
Before we knew it, the two of us resound together,
時に激しく 時に切なく
Sometimes passionately, sometimes sorrowfully.
響くは遠く 遥か彼方へ
Resounding far away, to the distant beyond,
やさしい歌は 世界を変える
A gentle song will change the world.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you...
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
The more precious someone is, the closer they are by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いてほしい
I just want it to reach you,
響け恋の歌
Resound, love song!
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Resound, love song!
あなたは気づく 二人は歩く
You realize, and the two of us walk on,
暗い道でも 日々照らす月
Even on dark roads, the moon shines on us daily.
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Never letting go of the hand I gripped tightly,
思いは強く 永遠誓う
My feelings grow stronger, swearing eternity.
永遠の淵 きっと僕は言う
At the abyss of eternity, I'm sure I'll say
思い変わらず 同じ言葉を
The very same words, with my feelings unchanged.
それでも足りず 涙にかわり
Even so, it's not enough, turning into tears,
喜びになり
turning into joy,
言葉にできず
unable to put into words,
ただ抱きしめる
I'll just hold you tight,
I'll just hold you tight.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you...
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
The more precious someone is, the closer they are by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いてほしい
I just want it to reach you,
響け恋の歌
Resound, love song!
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Resound, love song!
夢ならば 覚めないで
If this is a dream, don't wake me up,
If this is a dream, don't wake me up.
あなたと過ごした時
The time spent with you
永遠の星となる
Becomes an eternal star.
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you...
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
The more precious someone is, the closer they are by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いてほしい
I just want it to reach you,
響け恋の歌
Resound, love song!
ほら あなたにとって
Look, to you...
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
The more precious someone is, the closer they are by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ 届いてほしい
I just want it to reach you,
響け恋の歌
Resound, love song!
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Resound, love song!
はい！
Alright!
というわけで 皆さん 輪堂千速生誕祭に
So then, everyone, to the Rindou Chihaya Birthday Festival,
お越しくださり ありがとうございます！
thank you all so much for coming!
聞こえていますでしょうかー！
Can you guys hear me?!
挨拶します！
Time for greetings!
エンジン全開 レッツゴー！
Engine full throttle, let's go!
やばい
Oh dear...
爆走なDJ系 運転手担当 輪堂千速でーす！こんちはー！
I'm your wild driving DJ-type driver, Rindou Chihaya! Hello!
ということで 始まりました！
And so, it has begun!
初めての3D生誕ライブ！
My very first 3D birthday live stream!
いっぱい盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get super hyped up today!
配信のハッシュタグは
The hashtag for the stream is
右上... あ、こちらの
in the upper right... ah, this one right here!
ハッシュタグ 輪堂千速生誕祭2026 になるので
It's hashtag #輪堂千速生誕祭2026, so
たくさんポストしていただけると とても嬉しいです
I'd be super happy if you post a lot with it!
ちゃんと見ますからねー！
I'll definitely be checking them!
ぜひ トレンド1位とかになれたりしたら 嬉しいななんて思うので
It'd make me so happy if we could reach #1 on trending or something,
いっぱいスクショとかね 貼ってポスト...
so please post lots of screenshots and things...
そう言ってもらえると 嬉しーです！
I'm so happy to hear you say that!
わー！こんちは！ハイタッチありがとー！
Wow! Hello! Thanks for the high five!
ということでね 一旦ちょっと2曲歌わせていただいたので 振り返っていこうかなと思うんですが
So then! Since I've sung two songs so far, I thought we'd take a moment to look back on them,
まずは1曲目！「Driver's High」を 海沿いをフグタロウでドライブしながら歌わせていただきました！どうでしたでしょうか？
First off, for the first song, I sang "Driver's High" while driving along the coast with Fugutaro! How was it?
デビューの一番最初にラルクの曲を歌ってて で この「Driver's High」をいつか歌ってほしいってすごい言われていたので 絶対に生誕で歌おうと思って 1曲目に選んでみました！
Back when I debuted, the very first song I sang was by L'Arc, and so many people told me they wanted me to sing "Driver's High" someday! So I knew I had to sing it for my birthday, and picked it as the first song!
いや あの… まぁあの あそこカバーの私有地なので 色々諸々ひっくるめて… OKです！大丈夫！大丈夫！きっと大丈夫！
Well... you know, that place is COVER's private property, so taking everything into account... it's all OK! It's fine! It's fine! I'm sure it's fine!
そして2曲目！は 「小さな恋のうた」でした！どうでしたかー？
And the second song was "Chiisana Koi no Uta"! How was it?
そう！これ！
That's right! This!
千速が弾いてましたよ！
Chihaya was playing it!
いやあの ご存知の方も多いかなと思いますがね エレキを購入しまして練習していたんですが… あの 弾かせていただきました！
Well, as many of you probably know, I bought an electric guitar and have been practicing... and I played it!
やっぱりなんかエレキで初めて挑戦するのって なんか「小さな恋のうた」だよねっていうイメージがあってこの曲を選んだんですけど…
I had this image that the quintessential first song to try on electric guitar is "Chiisana Koi no Uta", which is why I chose it, but...
すんげー難しい！すんげー難しかったんですけど
It was super hard! It was super difficult, but...
でもね 生誕ライブでカッコいいところ見せたかったので いっぱい いっぱい いっぱい練習して… 弾けてたよね？なんとか！弾けてたと思います！
still, I wanted to show you all my cool side for my birthday live, so I practiced so, so much... I pulled it off, right? Somehow! I think I pulled it off!
なのでね いっぱい後でアーカイブとかも見直してくれるとうれしいです！ということで そしてね！
So I'd be really happy if you watch the archive again later! And with that...
お気づきの方もいますが 小さな恋のうた 最初は体育館だったんですけど 外に出てきましたよ！
As some of you might have noticed, during "Chiisana Koi no Uta" we started in a gymnasium, but now we've come outside!
やっぱ夏といえば外！海！山！自然！そして 夏の音楽と言えばフェスをイメージして
After all, summer means outdoors! The sea! Mountains! Nature! And when you think of summer music, you think of festivals, so...
夏フェス会場になっております！
we've turned this into a summer festival venue!
後ろにはね 海もあって 最高のロケーションで今日はフェスを開催していければなぁと思っております！
We've got the sea behind us too, and I hope we can hold a fest in this ultimate location today!
こんなにね 広いので あっちに行ったり… あ 予定にない動きをしてすみません本当に(笑) こっちに行ったりしていこうと思っています！
It's so spacious, so I'm thinking of moving over there... Ah, sorry for making unscripted movements, really! Or moving over here!
では まぁちょっとあんまり喋るとね あれなので 次の曲行こうと思うので ちょっと準備するのでギターとマイク置いてきます！ちょっと待っててね！いってきます！
Well, if I keep talking too much... yeah, so let me move on to the next song! I'll put my guitar and mic down to get ready. Wait a bit, okay? Be right back!
はーい！ということで！
Alright! So!
はい 来ました来ました！ということでここからはですね ゲストブロックになります！ので この後もいっぱい楽しんでいってください！
Alright, here we go, here we go! So from here on out, it's the guest block! Keep having tons of fun for the rest of the show!
盛り上がっていっくぞー！
Let me hear you get hyped!
GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers reckless and bold
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers staying true to our faith
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, right now (Bang!) Fire away like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!) ぶった斬っていこうぜ Get the fire!
Right here, right now (Burn!) Slash through it all, get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, right now (Bang!) Fire away like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
険しい修羅の道の中 他人の地図を広げて何処へ行く?
Navigating this harsh, ruthless path, where are you heading with someone else's map?
極色彩のカラスが それを奪い取って破り捨てた
A crow in vivid colors snatched it away and tore it to shreds
さぁ心の目 見開いて しかと今を見極めろ! (Yeah!)
Now open your mind's eye and gaze clearly at the present! (Yeah!)
失うモノなんてないさ いざ参ろう!
We've got nothing to lose, so let's go!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers reckless and bold
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers staying true to our faith
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, right now (Bang!) Fire away like a line drive!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
音を立てず忍び寄る影が いつも僕らを惑わせる
Shadows creep in without a sound, constantly leading us astray
有言実行 大きな風が うねりを上げて吹き荒れる
True to our words, a surging wind kicks up a raging storm
かざした鋭い刀で 己の未来切り開け! (Yeah!)
Unsheathe your sharp blade and carve out your own future! (Yeah!)
保証なんて どこにも無いさ なぁ そうだろ!?
There are no guarantees anywhere, isn't that right?!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers reckless and bold
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers staying true to our faith
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
信じるままに
As I believe,
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
Just go my way!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Fire it like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
I'll slash it through, get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Fire it like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
I'll slash it through, get the fire!
We are Fighting Dreamers
この仲間達と
With these friends,
Fighting Dreamers
全てを巻き込み
Involving everything,
Fighting Dreamers
志高く
With high ambitions!
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
We are Fighting Dreamers
高みを目指して
Aiming for the heights,
Fighting Dreamers
なりふり構わず
Without worrying about how I look,
Fighting Dreamers
信じるままに
As I believe!
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
Just go my way!
Don't forget your first impulse ever
Go my way!
Let's keep your adventurous ever
Don't forget your first impulse ever
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Fire it like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
I'll slash it through, get the fire!
Right here Right now (Bang!)
ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Fire it like a bullet liner!
Right here Right now (Burn!)
ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
I'll slash it through, get the fire!
カルマ
[Karma]
ガラス玉 ひとつ落とされた
A single marble fell to the ground
追いかけて もうひとつ落ちっこちた
As I chased after it, another fell
ひとつ分の陽だまりに
Within this sunlight made for one,
ひとつだけ残ってる
a single one remained
心臓が始まった時
From the moment our hearts started beating,
嫌でも人は場所を取る
people naturally take up space whether they want to or not
奪われない様に 守り続けてる
Continually protecting it so it won't be stolen
汚さずに保ってきた
Hands kept unsoiled
手でも汚れて見えた
still seemed dirty
記憶を疑う前に
Before doubting my memories,
記憶に疑われてる
my memories start to doubt me
必ず僕らは出会うだろう
For sure, we will meet each other,
同じ鼓動の音を目印にして
guided by the sound of our matching heartbeats
ここに居るよ いつだって呼んでるから
I'm right here, calling out to you always
くたびれた理由が重なって
When worn-out reasons overlap
揺れる時
and begin to waver,
生まれた意味を知る
I learn the meaning of my birth
存在が続く限り
As long as my existence continues,
仕方無いから場所を取る
it can't be helped—I must take my place
ひとつ分の陽だまりに
Within this sunlight made for one,
２つはちょっと入れない
two of us can't really fit
ガラス玉 ひとつ落とされた
A single marble fell to the ground
落ちた時 何か弾き出した
When it fell, something was pushed out
奪い取った場所で
In the place I took,
光を浴びた
I was basked in light
数えた足跡など
Counting the footprints I left behind,
気付けば数字でしかない
I realized they're nothing more than numbers
知らなきゃいけない事は
The thing I need to know
どうやら１と０の間
seems to lie somewhere between one and zero
初めて僕らは出会うだろう
For the first time, we will meet each other,
同じ悲鳴の旗を目印にして
guided by the banner of our matching cries
忘れないで いつだって呼んでるから
Don't ever forget, 'cause I'm calling to you always
重ねた理由を ２人で埋める時
When we bury our overlapping reasons together,
約束が交わされる
our promise is made
鏡なんだ 僕ら互いに
We are mirrors to each other,
それぞれのカルマを映す為の
reflecting our respective karma
汚れた手と手で触り合って
Touching with our dirty hands,
形が解る
we understand our true shape
ここに居るよ
I am right here
確かに触れるよ
You can feel me for sure
ひとり分の陽だまりに
Within this sunlight made for one,
僕らは居る
we exist together
忘れないで
Don't ever forget,
いつだって呼んでるから
'cause I'm always calling out to you
同じガラス玉の内側の方から
From inside the exact same marble
そうさ 必ず僕らは出会うだろう
That's right, for sure we will meet each other
沈めた理由に 十字架を建てる時
When we raise a cross over the buried reasons,
約束は果たされる
our promise will be fulfilled
僕らは ひとつになる
We will become as one
今日も君は 信じること
Are you waking up today without forgetting...
忘れずに目覚められていますか？
...what you believe in?
時が経つと 自分さえも
As time passes, in an era where...
信じれなくなる 時代のように
...you lose faith even in yourself,
自分では気付かないのが
the feature of this symptom...
この症状の特徴で
...is that you don't notice it yourself.
唯一ある予防法は
The only preventive measure...
「自分にウソだけはつかない事」
...is "never lying to yourself."
忘れてたまるもんかよ！！
As if I'd ever forget that!
僕がボクじゃなくなったら
If I stop being myself,
たとえ生きてたって
even if I'm still alive,
生きてる意味すら見つからんだろ！
I wouldn't find any meaning in living!
声にならない叫びは
For shouts that can't find a voice,
僕が声を枯らして
I'll sing until my voice goes hoarse,
叫んで歌って
screaming and singing,
伝わるまでわめいて
yelling until it gets through,
届くまで止めない！！
I won't stop until it reaches you!
今日も地球は 回り続ける
The Earth keeps spinning today as well,
誰が泣いても怒っても止まらず
without stopping no matter who cries or gets angry.
ためしに僕が 風邪をひいても
Even if I happen to catch a cold,
もちろん止まる事なんてねーわ！
of course it won't stop for me!
人生も同じように
Life moves forward the same way,
止まる事はなく進むし
without ever coming to a stop,
だからそうさ今日も人は
so that's why people today too...
お手手のシワとシワをあわせんの！
...press their hands together in prayer!
終わらせちまう事なんか
Anyone can just end things,
誰にだってできんだろ？！
right?!
たとえ終わっちまったって
Even if it comes to an end,
次のスタートすぐきれんだろ？！
you can make a new start right away, right?!
今キミが思うキセキも
If you raise the baseline...
底上げさせてしまえば
...of what you think is a miracle,
もうその時点で そのキセキは
then at that point, that miracle...
君にとっちゃ 必然のお仲間さ！
...becomes your inevitable companion!
WOW!!
何回ダメダメと言われようが
No matter how many times you're told "no,"
実際問題そんなん関係なくて
practically speaking, it doesn't matter!
今、自分自身必要なものたくわえてそろえとけよ！！
Gather and stock up on what you need right now!
なぁそうだろ？！
Isn't that right?!
まだまだ！！ 時間はまだあんぞ！！
Not yet!! You still have time!!
先見の明 今はとぎすまして
Sharpen your foresight right now!
主人公は一人だけ！！
There's only one protagonist!!
自分の物語のはじまり！！
The start of your own story!!
もうすぐ時計は6時
The clock will soon strike six,
もうそこに一番星
and the first star is already appearing.
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる 帰り道
Stepping on shadows, I want to melt into the night on my way home.
どんなに探してみても
No matter how hard I search,
ひとつしかない星
there's only one star.
何億光年 離れたところから
From hundreds of millions of light-years away,
あんなに 輝く
it shines so brightly.
いいな
How nice...
君は みんなから 愛されて
You are loved by everyone.
「いいや
"No,
僕はずっと 一人きりさ」
I've always been all alone."
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If I could become a constellation together with you,
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
on a starry night, that's my fleeting wish.
きらめいて ゆらめいて 震えているシグナル
Expressing ourselves in flickers, glimmers, and trembling signals.
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If I could become a constellation together with you,
空見上げて 指を差されるような
as if people would look up at the sky and point at us.
つないだ線 解かないで
Don't untie the line connecting us,
僕がどんなに 眩しくても
no matter how intensely I shine.
もうすぐ時計は 8時
It's almost 8 o'clock,
夜空に満点の星
the night sky is full of stars.
何億光年 離れたところにはもう
Hundreds of millions of light-years away,
ないかもしれない
they might not even be there anymore.
月が綺麗で 泣きそうになるのは
The moon was so beautiful it almost made me cry,
いつの日か 別れが来るから
because someday, we'll have to say goodbye.
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If I could become a constellation together with you,
彗星みたい 流れるひとりごと
like a comet, speaking my thoughts to myself.
消えていく残像は 真夜中のプリズム
The fading afterimages are a midnight prism.
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If I could become a constellation together with you,
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
if my earnest wish somehow reached someone,
変われるかな 夜の淵を
I wonder if I could change, tracing the edge of the night...
なぞるような こんな僕でも
even someone like me.
遥か彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Far away, we ended up meeting.
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
It's karma, so we'll keep meeting again and again.
雲の隙間まで
Even through the gaps in the clouds.
君と集まって 星座になれたら
If I could become a constellation together with you,
夜広げて 描こう 絵空事
let's paint the night with our dreams.
暗闇を 照らすような
Even if it's not a full moon
満月じゃなくても
that lights up the darkness,
だから集まって 星座になりたい
that's why I want to become a constellation together.
色とりどりの光 放つような
Shining in a rainbow of colorful light,
つないだ線 解かないよ
I won't untie the line connecting us,
君がどんなに 眩しくても
no matter how intensely you shine.
はい！ということで！ FLOW GLOWです！
All right! With that... we are FLOW GLOW!
イエーイ！
Yay!
聞いてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for listening!
はぁー... 大丈夫？ 息上がってんね
*Phew*... Are you okay? You're so out of breath!
ちょっと整えてね 大丈夫？
Take a moment to catch your breath. Are you okay?
あの FGでね ずっとバンドがやりたいと思ってたので
Um, we in FLOW GLOW have always wanted to play in a band,
まぁ 今日はちょっとエアバンドなんですけれどもね みんなで『星座になれたら』披露させていただきました！
so well, today was an air band performance, but we got to perform "If I Could Become a Constellation" together!
楽しかったー！
That was so much fun!
1回 自己紹介しとくか
Shall we quickly introduce ourselves?
オッケー！ じゃあ りっちゃんからいつもの順番でお願いします！
Okay! Ricchan, please start in our usual order!
はい！ 私の歌に酔いしれよ！ IN THE HOUSE!
Okay! Get drunk on my song! IN THE HOUSE!
FLOW GLOWの... ギター... ギターじゃない ベース担当！
FLOW GLOW's... guitar... wait, not guitar, bass player!
響咲リオナです！
I'm Isaki Riona!
低さ かっこよ！
That low voice is so cool!
ちーちゃん お誕生日おめでとう！
Chi-chan, happy birthday!
そして！
And next!
ニコたんが来たー！ hololive DEV_IS FLOW GLOWの
Niko-tan is here! From hololive DEV_IS FLOW GLOW,
なんだっけあれ？ キーボード！
what was it again? Keyboard!
キーボード担当 虎金妃笑虎だよー！
I'm the keyboard player, Koganei Niko!
みんな ありがとうー！
Thank you, everyone!
そして！
And next!
可愛く 痺れちゃう 充電足りてる？ hololive DEV_IS FLOW GLOWの
Cute and electrifying, got enough charge? From hololive DEV_IS FLOW GLOW,
ドラム担当 水宮枢でーす！
I'm the drummer, Mizumiya Su!
ちーはー お誕生日おめでとうー！
Chihaya, happy birthday!
そして！
And next!
あ はい！
Ah, yes!
せーの！ うー... ビービー！
One, two, three! Uuu... Bibi!
ちょっと待って、キラキラな
Wait a sec, I'm the sparkling...
キラキラ・ラ・ビビです！
Sparkling Ra Bibi!
あ、忘れてた。ビビはギター担当！
Ah, I forgot! Bibi is on guitar!
千早お誕生日おめでとう！
Happy Birthday, Chihaya!
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
みんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all so much for coming!
なんかいいお知らせがあるんじゃないの？
Isn't there some good news to announce?
なんと、トレンド1位になったー！
We actually hit #1 on trending!
やったー！嬉しいー！
Yay! I'm so happy!
今まで流行って2位とかで、トレンドに乗れなかったから...
Up until now, we only peaked at #2 and couldn't hit #1...
こんな嬉しい誕生日のプレゼントをいただき、本当にありがとうございます！
So receiving such an incredible birthday present makes me so grateful! Thank you!
いっぱいツイートしてくれてありがとう！もっとツイートしてね！
Thank you for tweeting so much! Keep them coming!
『星座になれたら』を披露しましたけど、皆さんどうでしたか？
We just performed "If I Could Become a Constellation", how was it?
楽しかった！ドラムを叩きたくなりました！
It was so fun! It made me want to play the drums!
めっちゃ似合ってた！実は経験者なんです。
You looked great on drums! - I actually have experience.
いつかFGバンドを結成したいの。
I want to form an FG band someday!
今回はエアバンドだったので、ニコたんにはキーボードを担当してもらったんですけど...
Since we were an air band this time, Niko-tan played keyboard...
すごかったでしょ？指さばきが！
Wasn't she amazing? Her fingerwork!
すごかった！本当すごかった！
It was incredible! Truly amazing!
全身で弾いてくれてたもんね。
She was playing with her whole body.
いつでもやるよ、マジで。
I'll do it anytime, seriously.
いや、出来ひん出来ひん。一音も触れずにね。
No way, you can't actually play! Without touching a single key!
これ最高！最高！
This is awesome! Awesome!
自分もすごい楽しかったし、みんなも楽しそうにしてくれてとっても嬉しかったです！
I had a blast myself, and seeing everyone enjoy it made me so happy!
いつか実現させましょう！ - 絶対したい！
Let's make it happen someday! - Absolutely!
そんな時はみんな今回の楽器でいいんですか？
For that, is everyone okay with their current instruments?
うん。 - え？あれ？
Yep. - Wait, what?
楽器がやりたいって... - 歌、歌う！
I want to play an instrument... - I'll sing!
ダメダメ！ケンカだ！
No way! Fight! It's a fight!
ニコたんはさ、やるとしたら何の楽器やりたい？
Niko-tan, if you were to play, what instrument would you want?
何でもいいよ！ - 出まくってるよね！
Anything is fine! - You're hogging all the spotlight!
ギター、ドラム、ベースがいるんだけど...
Right now we have guitars, drums, and bass...
そう言ったらやっぱりキーボードしかない...
In that case, keyboard is the only choice...
バイオリンがいける！
Violin works!
バイオリンが入ってるバンドめちゃかっこいいよ！
A band with a violin sounds super cool!
打楽器はどう？トライアングルとか。
How about percussion? Like a triangle.
カスタネットとか！タンバリン！
Or castanets! Tambourine!
全員で打楽器バンド？
A full percussion band with everyone?
シンバル！ - 全然違うタイプになるからやめろ！
Cymbals! - Stop that, that'd be a totally different genre!
そういうのもやってみたい！楽しそう！
I'd love to try that too! Sounds fun!
FGの企画とかでやったりするのね。
We could do it as a special FG project!
やろう！やりましょう！
Let's do it! Let's do it!
ということでね、今回はFGちゃんたちに来ていただきました。
So today, we were joined by the FG girls.
リハーサルから長い時間付き合ってもらって、本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for hanging with us from rehearsals onward!
おめでとう！ - ありがとう！
Happy Birthday! - Thank you!
千早が何でもします券を皆様に贈呈しますので。
I'll give everyone a "Chihaya Will Do Anything" coupon!
マジで？何でも？一人1枚？
Really? Anything? One ticket each?
一旦1枚！ - やったー！
One ticket for now! - Yay!
取り消し！取り消し券！
Cancel that! Revocation ticket!
千早、美味しいご飯ごちそうさまー！
Chihaya, thanks for treating us to delicious food!
それはもちろん全員におごらせていただきます！
I will definitely treat all of you!
今日のお弁当も豪華だったしね！
Today's bento boxes were luxurious too!
奮発しました！喜んでいただけて良かった！
I splurged on them! I'm glad you liked them!
まだあるので持って帰ってください。
There's still more left, so please take some home.
ではそろそろ次の曲に行きたいと思います！
Now then, let's move on to our next song!
みんなも見届けてくれるかな？ - バッチリ見届けるよ！
Will everyone keep watching? - We definitely will!
ライブを見てくれてるみんなも、まだまだ盛り上がっていってくださいね！
To everyone watching the live stream, keep the hype going!
イエーイ！行けー！
Yay! Go for it!
まだコメント欄は『何でも』って言ってる。
The comment section is still talking about "Anything".
リスナーさんたちには何もしないですけど、FGちゃんたちには何でもしてあげたい気持ちです！
I won't do "anything" for the listeners, but I want to do anything for FG!
気持ちだけじゃなくてね！ - お願いします！
Not just in spirit! - Please!
それじゃあ、みんなハイ！ありがとうね！
Alright then, everyone... bye! Thank you!
俺も一緒に行こう！シュッ シュッ...
I'll go with you too! Whoosh, whoosh...
打上花火
[Fireworks]
あの日見渡した渚を
I can still remember the shore we saw that day...
今も思い出すんだ
even now.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
The words we carved into the sand...
君の後ろ姿
the sight of you from behind.
寄り返す波が
The returning waves
足元をよぎり
pass by my feet
何かをさらう
and wash something away.
夕凪の中
In the evening calm,
日暮れだけが通り過ぎて行く
only the dusk passes by.
パッと光って咲いた
Fireworks bloomed in a flash of light,
花火を見ていた
and we were watching them.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely this summer is not over yet.
曖昧な心を
Unraveling our uncertain hearts
溶かして繋いだ
and tying them together,
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to go on forever.
あと何度君と同じ花火を見られるかなって
Wondering how many more times I can see the same fireworks with you,
笑う顔に何が出来るだろうか
I wonder what I can do for your smiling face.
傷つくこと 喜ぶこと
Getting hurt, feeling happy,
繰り返す波と情動
repeating waves and emotions,
焦燥 最終列車の音
impatience, and the sound of the last train.
何度でも言葉にして君を呼ぶよ
I'll put it into words and call your name again and again,
波間を選び もう一度
choosing the space between waves, once more...
もう二度と悲しまずに済むように
So that you'll never have to feel sad again,
包むように
gently wrapping around you.
ハッと息を飲めば
If I gasp in surprise,
消えちゃいそうな光が
a light that seemed about to vanish
きっとまだ胸に住んでいた
was surely still living in my heart.
手を伸ばせば触れた
Reaching out my hand, I touched it—
あったかい未来は
a warm future
密かに二人を見ていた
was secretly watching over the two of us.
パッと花火が
Fireworks suddenly
夜に咲いた
bloomed in the night,
夜に咲いて
静かに消えた
and quietly vanished.
離さないで
Don't let go,
もう少しだけ
just a little longer,
もう少しだけ このままで
just a little longer, stay like this.
あの日見渡した渚を
The shore we looked out upon that day,
今も思い出すんだ
I still remember it even now.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
The words carved in the sand,
君の後ろ姿
and the sight of your back.
パッと光って咲いた
Fireworks bloomed in a flash of light,
花火を見ていた
and we were watching them.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely this summer is not over yet.
曖昧な心を
Unraveling our uncertain hearts
溶かして繋いだ
and tying them together,
この夜が続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to go on forever.
ららら...
La la la...
ソラニン
[Song: Solanin]
思い違いは空のかなた
Mistaken thoughts lie beyond the sky,
さよならだけの人生か
is life nothing but goodbyes?
ほんの少しの未来は見えたのに
Even though I saw just a glimpse of the future...
Even though I could see a bit of the future,
さよならなんだ
it's goodbye.
昔住んでた小さな部屋は
The small room I used to live in
今は誰かが住んでんだ
is now lived in by someone else.
君に言われたひどい言葉も
Even the harsh words you said to me,
無駄な気がした毎日も
and the days that felt meaningless,
あの時こうしていれば
if I had done this back then,
あの日に戻れれば
if I could go back to that day...
あの頃の僕にはもう戻れないよ
I can never go back to who I was back then.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
Even if a gentle happiness
だらっと続いたとする
were to drag on idly,
きっと悪い種が芽を出して
a bad seed would surely sprout,
もうさよならなんだ
and it would be goodbye already.
寒い冬の冷えた缶コーヒー
A cold canned coffee in the freezing winter,
虹色の長いマフラー
a long rainbow-colored scarf,
小走りで路地裏を抜けて
cutting through the back alleys at a jog,
思い出してみる
I try to remember.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
Even if a gentle happiness
だらっと続いたとする
were to drag on idly,
きっと悪い種が芽を出して
a bad seed would surely sprout,
もうさよならなんだ
and it would be goodbye already.
なんだ
It's goodbye...
It's...
なんだ
さよなら それもいいさ
Goodbye, that's fine too.
どこかで元気でやれよ
Stay healthy out there somewhere.
さよなら 僕もどうにかやるさ
Goodbye, I'll manage somehow too.
さよなら そうするよ
Goodbye, that's what I'll do.
はい！
Alright!
はい、ということで「ソラニン」をお送りしました！いかがだったでしょうかー？
Yes, so that was "Solanin"! How did you like it?
いや、あの、見覚えがある方もいらっしゃるのではないでしょうか？
Well, I think some of you might recognize this setup, right?
これ、まあ初めて見る方もいらっしゃるかなと思うんですが
Though I suppose some of you might be seeing this for the first time...
あの、3Dお披露目の時にも、ギターの弾き語りを披露させていただいたんですけれど、その時よりもレベルアップできていたでしょうか？
During my 3D debut, I also performed an acoustic guitar sing-along, but do you think I've leveled up since then?
初めて多分最初の頃に練習したのがソラニンで、そこからずっとちゃんと出来た姿をみんなに見せたかったのでこの曲を選びました！
Solanin was probably the very first song I practiced back then, and I've always wanted to show everyone a proper performance, so I chose this song!
そしてですね、ギター千速の音だけじゃなくて、もう一本ソロとかベースがあったと思うんですが
And also, besides my guitar sound, you probably noticed another guitar solo and bass line, right?
それはですね、千速のギターの先生に一緒に弾いていただきました！
That was played together with my guitar teacher!
なんかレッスンの時にセッションしてたら「え、めっちゃかっこよくね？」ってなって、「先生もよかったら一緒に弾いてくれませんか？」って言って、一緒にね、弾いていただきました！ありがとうございましたー！
During a lesson, we were jamming together and thought, "Wait, isn't this super cool?" So I asked, "Teacher, would you like to play along with me?" and we ended up playing together! Thank you so much!
ということでね、一旦ここまでの振り返りをしていこうかなと思いますよ！
And so, I think I'll do a quick recap of everything so far!
まずは、ゲストパートで1曲目が...
First, in the guest part, the first song was...
1884で
With "1884"...
「Fighting Dreamer」しました！
...we performed "Fighting Dreamer"!
どうですか？やっぱり1曲目はぶち上げていきたいなと思って
How was it? I really wanted to hype everyone up with the first song,
1884でめっちゃ盛り上がる曲を選びました！
so I picked a super hype song by 1884!
先輩たちのぶち上げがカッコよくて「チハも頑張るぞ！」ってなったので、楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです！
Seeing my seniors get everyone hype inspired me, so I hope you enjoyed it!
そして2曲目はトワ様と「カルマ」を歌いました！
And for the second song, I sang "Karma" with Towa-sama!
やっぱトワ様の低音が大好きなので、ちょっと無理を言って原曲キーでね
I love Towa-sama's low notes, so I pressed a bit and we sang it in the original key,
すごい低い中、一緒に歌っていただきました！
so even though it was really low, she sang it with me!
トワ様ありがとうございます！めっちゃカッコよかったです！
Thank you so much, Towa-sama! It was super cool!
そして3曲目がルイ先輩と「ジブンロック」！
And the third song was "Jibun Rock" with Lui-senpai!
いや、カッコよすぎない？ルイ先輩カッコよすぎない？ヤバいんですけど！
Wasn't that way too cool? Wasn't Lui-senpai way too cool? It was incredible!
あの、本当にルイ先輩のカッコいい...
Seriously, Lui-senpai's cool...
ちょっとこう、がなりの効いた、エッジの効いた声で
...raspy and edgy voice...
歌いたいなと思ってこの曲を選びました！超カッコよかったよね！
...made me really want to sing this song! It was so cool, right?
そして6曲目が「セツナになれたら」
And for the 6th song, "Setsuna ni Naretara"...
さっきね、フシギちゃんたちと一緒にワイワイした「セツナになれたら」で
Earlier, we had so much fun singing "Setsuna ni Naretara" with Fushigi-chan and others!
7曲目！激エモの...
And the 7th song! Super emotional...
にゃんちゃん、おかゆ先輩との「打上花火」！
..."Uchiage Hanabi" with Nyan-chan and Okayu-senpai!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
もうマジ...あの本当におにぎりの皆さんには申し訳ないんですけれど
Honestly, I'm so sorry to all the Onigirya fans,
あの瞬間はちょっと自認・おかゆ先輩の彼氏のつもりで「モ〜！」って
but in that moment, I kind of felt like Okayu-senpai's boyfriend, and...
やってしまいました！
...I totally got carried away!
もう最高でした、ありがとうございました、本当に！お返しします、すみません！
It was the best, thank you so much! I'll give her back now, sorry!
というね、エモエモな...カッコいいからエモまでのパートがありましたけれど
So we had that sequence from cool to super emotional,
楽しんでいただけてますか〜？
are you all enjoying it so far?
ちょっとコメント見てみようかな！
Let me check the comments for a second!
あ、「エモすぎた」「泣いた」え、わかる！
"Too emotional," "I cried." Ah, I know, right?!
わかる！めっちゃエモいよね！
I know! It was super emotional, right?
チハもなんかやりながら「エモすぎるこれ！」と思ってやってましたよー！
While performing, Chihaya was thinking "This is way too emotional!" too!
ありがとう！めっちゃよかったよね！
Thank you! It was really great, wasn't it?
さあ！ということでね！
Now then! Moving on!
ちょっとね、チハ喋らせると喋り過ぎてしまうので、次のパートに行きたいんですが
If you let Chihaya talk, she'll talk way too much, so I want to move on to the next part,
ここからは嬉しいお知らせとなります！
but from here, we have some exciting announcements!
輪堂千速 誕生記念 2026 グッズ販売のお知らせとなります！
This is an announcement for Rindo Chihaya Birthday Celebration 2026 Goods Sales!
生誕グッズが出るぞー！こちらをご覧ください、ドン！
Birthday merch is coming out! Please take a look at this, boom!
はい！盛りだくさんですねー！
Yes! There's so much packed in here!
イラストはトリダモノ先生ママに描いていただきました！ありがとうございます！
The illustration was drawn by Toridamono-sensei Mama! Thank you so much!
ギターを弾いてるライブの一シーンをイメージして描いていただきました！いや、めっちゃカッコいいよね！
She drew it based on a live performance scene playing the guitar! Isn't it super cool?
それではね、詳細を見ていきましょう！まずは、こちら！
Now then, let's look at the details! First up is this!
Chihaya BD Fes Tシャツ 2026 でございます！
It's the "Chihaya BD Fes T-shirt 2026"!
キービジュアルのイラスト全身を使用した、カッコ可愛いTシャツです！
It's a cool and cute T-shirt featuring the full-body key visual illustration!
バンドTシャツっぽくしたくて、ちょっとロゴとかイカつい感じにしてもらったので
I wanted it to feel like a band tee, so I had the logo made a bit aggressive and cool,
ぜひぜひライブとか日常でも着てもらえたら嬉しいです！
so I'd be really happy if you wear it at live shows or in daily life!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ピックケースキーホルダーです！
It's the "Pick Case Keyholder"!
お気に入りのピックを入れておしゃれに持ち運べるキーホルダーです！
It's a keyholder that lets you stylishly carry your favorite pick!
キーホルダーがメインで、3枚のピックは付属品としてついています。
The keyholder is the main item, and 3 picks are included as accessories.
ピックケースホルダーにはピックが1枚入る仕様です。
The pick case holder is designed to hold one pick.
今回のために書いたサインとかロゴとか...
The picks feature my signature written for this occasion, the logo...
あとは「FlatOut」というロゴ、今回のタイトルのロゴが描かれてるピックがセットになっています！
...and the "FlatOut" logo, which is the title of this event, all included in the set!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
ちはとお出かけバッグです！
It's the "Chihaya Outing Bag"!
前にポーチがついていて、前のポーチをひっくり返すと...
It has a pouch on the front, and if you turn the front pouch inside out...
中身を見せて推しバッグにチェンジできる...
...you can show off the inside and turn it into an "oshi bag",
ちょっと機能性のある斜めがけのバッグになっています！
making it a functional crossbody bag!
いろんなところ、これでお出かけしてください！
Please go out to all kinds of places with this!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
どこでもふぐ太郎ティッシュカバー！
The "Everywhere Fugutaro Tissue Cover"!
ふんわりとした質感のふぐ太郎モチーフのティッシュカバーです！
It's a tissue cover styled after Fugutaro with a soft texture!
あ、可愛いよね！
Ah, isn't it cute?
お家でも車でも職場でもふぐ太郎を連れて行けます！
You can bring Fugutaro with you at home, in the car, or at work!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
シチュエーションボイスです！
It's the Situation Voice!
タイトルは「ライブリハーサルボイス」！
The title is "Live Rehearsal Voice"!
ライブ前のリハーサルでドキドキ緊張してるチハのシチュエーションボイスになっておりますので
It's a situation voice of a nervous, heart-pounding Chihaya before the rehearsal,
ドキドキの緊張感をぜひ聴きに来てください！
so please come listen to that thrilling tension!
そしてフルセット購入特典もあります！こちら！
And there's also a Full Set Purchase Bonus! Here it is!
直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードです！
It's a Cheki-style bromide card with a hand-signed signature & foil-stamped message!
全部直筆でチハヤがサインを書きますのでね
Chihaya will personally hand-sign every single one of them,
ぜひぜひフルセットで購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです！
so I'd be super happy if you purchase the full set!
そして特典ボイス、タイトルは「ライブ後、君と」になります！
And the bonus voice title is "After the Live, With You"!
先ほどのボイスと合わせて聴くと、またよりエモさを感じられるのではないかなと思うので
If you listen to it along with the previous voice, you'll feel even more emotion,
ぜひこちらも聴いてみてください！
so please give this one a listen too!
改めてフルセットはこちらになります！
Once again, here is the full set!
いやね、これ全部Tシャツ着て
Seriously, wearing this T-shirt,
バッグ持って、キーホルダー付けて、ふぐ太郎持って
carrying the bag, attaching the keyholder, holding Fugutaro,
どこでも行けるチハヤセット！
it's the "Go Anywhere Chihaya Set"!
まあ、買うならフルセットの方がいいよね！
Well, if you're buying, the full set is definitely better!
21時、この後21時カートオープンとなりますので
The shop cart opens at 21:00 right after this,
数量限定ではないので、ぜひね
and it's not limited in quantity, so please...
ゆっくり購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです！よろしくお願いします！
I'd be so happy if you could purchase at your own pace! Thank you so much!
お願いします
Thank you!
そして皆様待望のお知らせがございます！
And now, we have an announcement everyone's been eagerly waiting for!
こちら！
Take a look at this!
なんと、林堂千速ソロとして初めてのオリ曲「Flatout」が
Rindo Chihaya's very first solo original song, "Flatout"...
このあと24時、7月9日木曜日の0時、このあとね、3時間チョイ後ぐらいからデジタルリリースされます！
...will be released digitally today at midnight, 12:00 AM on Thursday, July 9th! In a little over 3 hours!
やったー！
Yay!
このポーズしてる。今回のライブのタイトルにもなっている「Flatout」はオリ曲のタイトルでございました！
She's doing this pose. "Flatout," which is also the title of this live, was actually the title of my original song!
えー、この配信が終わった後にMVが公開されますので、そちらもぜひお楽しみに！
The MV will be released right after this stream ends, so please look forward to that as well!
概要欄にね、そのうちたぶんリンクが貼られたり貼られなかったりすると思うので、そちらもチェックしてみてください。
The link will probably be posted in the description sooner or later, so be sure to check that out too.
新曲、このあとやっぱ早速聴きたいですよね？このあと披露するので絶対聴いてください！
I'm sure you want to hear the new song right away, right? I'll be performing it next, so please stay tuned!
最後まで、最後までね、チャンネルはそのままで見ていってくださいね。
Please keep watching on this channel until the very end, okay?
以上、林堂千速生誕祭2026のグッズ情報とリリース情報でした！みんな買ってね！サブスクでも聴いてね！
That's all for the merch and release info for Rindo Chihaya Birthday Fes 2026! Everyone, please buy them and stream the song!
はい、ということで怒涛のお知らせコーナーでした。
Alright! That was our whirlwind announcement segment.
ここからいよいよライブもクライマックスです！でも、まだまだあります！
The live performance is finally reaching its climax! But there's still more to come!
盛り上がる準備できてますか？最後一緒にぶち上げていこうね！
Are you ready to get hyped? Let’s turn it up together until the very end!
では、準備してきます。
Now then, I'm going to get ready.
そのチャンネルはそのままで。
Keep watching on this channel.
I wanna fly so high Yeah, I know my wings are dried
「翼仰げば」って人は云う
People say, "If you spread your wings..."
その向こうにあるは無情 飛べる者 落ちる者
But what lies beyond is heartlessness for those who fly and those who fall.
誰も見てない 気にも留めない それでも飛び続けた
No one is watching, no one even cares, yet I kept on flying.
傷ついた言葉乗せ 運びたいから
Because I want to carry those wounded words along.
追いかけて届くよう 僕等一心に羽ばたいて
Let's chase after it to reach it, as we earnestly flap our wings.
問いかけて嘆いた夜 故郷は一層輝いて
On the night I questioned and grieved, my hometown shone all the brighter.
ワタリドリの様に今 旅に発つよ
Now, like a migratory bird, I set off on a journey.
ありもしないストーリーを 描いてみせるよ
I'll show you I can paint a story that doesn't even exist.
I wanna fly so far Away with my guitar
「一人じゃない」って人々は歌う
People sing, "You are not alone."
間違いじゃない 理想論でもない ただ頼って生きたくはない
It's not wrong, nor is it idealism, I just don't want to live depending on others.
誰も聴いてない 気にも留めない それでも歌い続けた
No one is listening, no one even cares, yet I kept on singing.
傷ついたあなたを 笑わせたいから
Because I want to make you smile when you're hurt.
追い風届けるよ 僕等一心に羽ばたいて
I'll send a tailwind to you, as we earnestly flap our wings.
遠い過去を背負ってた あなたを未来へ運ぶよ
I'll carry you, who bore a distant past, into the future.
ワタリドリの様に今 群れをなして
Now, like migratory birds, forming a flock,
大それた四重奏を 奏で終える日まで
until the day we finish playing this grand quartet.
All this time we come and we grow And now it's time that we should go
But we both know that this is for sure It's not the end of the world Well, see you one day
追いかけて届くよう 僕等一心に羽ばたいて
Let's chase after it to reach it, as we earnestly flap our wings.
問いかけて嘆いた夜 朝焼け色に染まっていく
The night I questioned and grieved turns into the colors of sunrise.
ワタリドリの様にいつか 舞い戻るよ
Like a migratory bird, I will fly back someday.
ありもしないストーリーを いつかまた会う日まで
With a story that doesn't even exist, until the day we meet again.
いつかまた会う日まで
Until the day we meet again
Shiny Smily Story (2022 ver.)
はいということで、輪堂千速生誕祭、ここまで見てくれたみんな本当にありがとうございます！
All right then! Thank you so much, everyone who watched Rindo Chihaya's Birthday Festival this far!
次が本当にラストの曲です。
The next one is truly the last song.
この曲は、いつかみんなと現地で会ってライブができた時に、最後に歌えたらいいなーって、そんな思いで千速のいろんな気持ちを込めて作ってもらった曲です。
I had this song made with all my feelings packed into it, hoping that when I can finally perform live with you all in person, I'd get to sing this at the end.
千速の初めてのオリ曲、聴いてください。『Flat out』
Please listen to Chihaya's very first original song, "Flat out".
メランコリーのリフレイン 午前3時
A melancholy refrain at 3 a.m.
夢を見るには少し遅すぎた Midnight
A midnight that's a bit too late for dreaming.
言葉にならないままの想いが
Before these unexpressed feelings
溢れだしてしまう前に 飛び出した部屋 光を見たくて
overflow, I ran out of my room, wanting to see the light.
"どうせ"だって 何度だって 諦めようとしたって
No matter how many times I thought "what's the use" and tried to give up,
"だけど""きっと" 今日もそっと 伸ばした手 あの星まで
saying "and yet" and "surely," today again I quietly reach out toward that star.
自分さえだませない 嘘はもうやめて 踏み込め
Stop telling lies that can't even fool yourself, and step on the gas!
駆け抜けて 音も風も抜き去って 迷いさえも振り切って
Dash through, leaving both sound and wind behind, shaking off even my doubts!
スピードを上げて
Pick up the speed!
行なくちゃ 夜のまだその向こうへ
I have to go, far beyond this night!
見たこともない世界へ 今最高速度で
To a world I've never seen, now at top speed!
高鳴る方へ 答えなんてなくたって
Toward where my heart throbs, even without any answers!
ただこうしていたいだけ 未完成で不完全な道の先まで
I just want to be like this, all the way to the end of this unfinished, imperfect road.
行ける 信じて
Believing I can make it!
差し障りないように生きた日々
Days spent living to avoid trouble,
諦めの言い訳を探すのやめて
I stopped looking for excuses to give up.
もどかしい気持ち 窓の向こうに 輝くあの星みたいになりたかったんだ
Frustrated feelings... I wanted to become like that star shining beyond the window.
足りない物だらけだって どれだけ離されたって 止まればそこまでなんだ
Even if I'm full of flaws, no matter how far behind I am, stopping means it's over!
進め 進め 未来を変える瞬間は いつかじゃなくて今なんだ
Forge ahead! Forge ahead! The moment to change the future isn't "someday", it's NOW!
進め 進め 先へ
Forge ahead! Forge ahead! Moving forward!
もっと遠くまで
Even further away!
確かめに行くんだ Flat out
I'm going to find out, Flat out!
駆け抜けて 夢に見たその舞台へ
Dash through to that stage I dreamed of!
決して振り返らないで スピードを上げて
Never look back! Pick up the speed!
行なくちゃ 夜のまだその向こうへ
I have to go, far beyond this night!
見たこともない世界へ 今最高速度で
To a world I've never seen, now at top speed!
信じる方へ 答えなんてなくたって
Toward what I believe in, even without any answers!
ただこうして走り出したんだ 止まらないよ
I just started running like this, and I won't stop!
さあ あの星に届け
Now, reach that star!
輪堂千速生誕祭2026、見ていただいて本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you all so much for watching Rindo Chihaya Birthday Festival 2026!
これからもみんなと向こう側の景色たくさん見に行きたいです！
I want to see so many views on the other side with everyone from now on too!
これからも千速のこと好きでいてついてきてくれたら嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if you continue to love Chihaya and follow along!
本当に今日はありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for today!
ありがとねー！
Thank you!
輪堂千速生誕LIVE お越しいただきありがとうございます 初めてのライブはどうでしたか？？ 見てくれたみんなのおかげで最高の1日になりました いつかキミの声が直接きけるその時まで これからも走り続けるよ！！！ 今日は本当にありがとう
[On-screen Note: Rindo Chihaya Birthday LIVE. Thank you for coming! How was my first live concert?? Thanks to everyone who watched, it became the best day ever. Until the day I can hear your voice in person, I'll keep running forward!!! Thank you so much for today!]
輪堂千速 生誕 LIVE
[Rindo Chihaya Birthday LIVE]
お越しいただきありがとうございます
Thank you so much for coming!
初めてのライブはどうでしたか？？
How was my first live show??
見に来てくれたキミがいて初めて完成します
It's only complete because you came to watch.
いつかキミの声が"直接"きけるその時まで
Until the day comes when I can hear your voice in person,
これからも走り続けるよ！！！
I'll keep running forward!!!
今日は本当にありがとう
Thank you so much for today!